Tufts ALLIES Records UA248
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts ALLIES Records
2006 -- 2018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
UA248
3 Gigabytes
13 Digital Object(s) 13 digital objects containing 1376 files.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Tufts ALLIES, 2018, accession UA-2018-047.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in thirteen series. The first twelve series are arranged by academic year from 2006 through 2018, with one additional undated series.
Biographical / Historical
The Alliance Linking Leaders in Education and the Services (ALLIES) is an undergraduate organization that works to bridge the civil-military gap, foster lasting relationships between future civilian and military leaders, and improve general discourse and understanding of global affairs. Three Tufts students – Peter Maher ('07), Susannah Hamblin ('07), and Padden Murphy ('09) – cofounded ALLIES in 2006. Tufts ALLIES' three original partner institutions were the U.S. Military Academy at West Point, the U.S. Naval Academy at Annapolis, and the U.S. Air Force Academy at Colorado Springs. As of 2018, seven schools have active chapters, and several others are in development. In addition to holding weekly discussion meetings, Tufts ALLIES hosts two major annual events: the Civil-Military Relations Conference (CMRC), and the Field Exercise in Peace and Stability Operations (FieldEx). Tufts also partners with other ALLIES chapters on the annual Joint Research Project (JRP).
Scope and Contents
This collection contains photographs and documentation of ALLIES events and programs; annual reports, newsletters, and other publications by or about ALLIES, including IGL reports; and materials relating to the mission and history of the group.
Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student life; Student activism; Foreign affairs
- 2006-2007 files, UA248.001; 9.4 Megabytes
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in received order.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is open for research.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains an IGL Report and the ALLIES newsletter.
  - 2006 -- 2007 files, UA248.001.00001; 2 Digital Object(s); 9.4 Megabytes
    Open for research.
    This files includes an IGL Report and the ALLIES newsletter.
- 2007-2008 files, UA248.002; 23.6 Megabytes
  This series contains an IGL Report, the ALLIES newsletter, ALLIES working documents, and a photograph.
  - 2007 -- 2008 files, UA248.002.00001; 11 Digital Object(s); 23.6 Megabytes
    This files includes an IGL Report, the ALLIES newsletter, ALLIES working documents, and a photograph.
- 2008-2009 files, UA248.003; 29 Megabytes
  This series contains an IGL report.
  - 2008 -- 2009 files, UA248.003.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 29 Megabytes
    This file includes an IGL Report.
- 2009-2010 files, UA248.004; 14.2 Megabytes
  This series contains ALLIES working documents, including a history of the group.
  - 2009 -- 2010 files, UA248.004.00001; 7 Digital Object(s); 14.2 Megabytes
    This file includes ALLIES working documents, including a history of the group.
- 2010-2011 files, UA248.005; 15.1 Megabytes
  This series contains an IGL Report and a calendar of events.
  - 2010 -- 2011 files, UA248.005.00001; 2 Digital Object(s); 15.1 Megabytes
    This file includes an IGL Report and a calendar of events.
- 2011-2012 files, UA248.006; 1 Megabytes
  This series contains an IGL Report and ALLIES working documents, program documentation, and photographs.
  - 2011 -- 2012 files, UA248.006.00001; 69 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes
    This file includes an IGL Report and ALLIES working documents, program documentation, and photographs.
- 2012-2013 files, UA248.007; 502.5 Megabytes
  This series contains ALLIES photographs, publications, and working documents.
  - 2012 -- 2013 files, UA248.007.00001; 125 Digital Object(s); 502.5 Megabytes
    This file includes ALLIES photographs, publications, and working documents.
- 2013-2014 files, UA248.008; 17.5 Megabytes
  This series contains the ALLIES annual report, photographs, and working documents.
  - 2013 -- 2014 files, UA248.008.00001; 194 Digital Object(s); 17.5 Megabytes
    This file includes the ALLIES annual report, photographs, and working documents.
- 2014-2015 files, UA248.009; 232 Megabytes
  This series contains photographs and working documents related to ALLIES events including FieldEx and CMRC, as well as publicity materials.
  - 2014 -- 2015 files, UA248.009.00001; 296 Digital Object(s); 232 Megabytes
    This file includes photographs and working documents related to ALLIES events including FieldEx and CMRC, as well as publicity materials.
- 2015-2016 files, UA248.010; 1.5 Megabytes
  This series includes an ALLIES annual report, photographs and working documents related to ALLIES events including FieldEx and CMRC, and other miscellaneous photographs. This series also includes two ALLIES 10th anniversary coins.
  - 2015 -- 2016 files, UA248.010.00001; 344 Digital Object(s); 1.5 Gigabytes
    This file includes an ALLIES annual report, photographs and working documents related to ALLIES events including FieldEx and CMRC, and other miscellaneous photographs.
  - 10th anniversary coins, 2016; UA248.010.001; .1 Linear Feet (Box Shared 12)
- 2016-2017 files, UA248.011; 146.9 Megabytes
  This series contains ALLIES annual report; photographs and working documents related to ALLIES events including FieldEx, CMRC, JRP Japan, and Tactical SIM; and other miscellaneous photographs and working documents.
  - 2016 -- 2017 files, UA248.011.00001; 160 Digital Object(s); 146.9 Megabytes
    This file includes an ALLIES annual report; photographs and working documents related to ALLIES events including FieldEx, CMRC, JRP Japan, and Tactical SIM; and other miscellaneous photographs and working documents.
- 2017-2018 files, UA248.012; 327.8 Megabytes
  This series contains ALLIES publicity material such as a calendar of meetings and a group description and powerpoint, as well as photographs and working documents related to CMRC.
  - 2017 -- 2018 files, UA248.012.00001; 128 Digital Object(s); 327.8 Megabytes
    This file includes ALLIES publicity material such as a calendar of meetings and a group description and powerpoint, as well as photographs and working documents related to CMRC.
- Undated files, 2006 -- 2018; UA248.013; 27 Megabytes
  This series contains miscellaneous photographs and working documents, including an ALLIES logo and letterhead and documents related to the ALLIES History Project.
  - Undated files, circa 2006 -- 2018; UA248.013.00001; 37 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes
    This file includes miscellaneous photographs and working documents, including an ALLIES logo and letterhead and documents related to the ALLIES History Project.